Maali Abdurrahman Al-Wohaibi

☑ maali.alwohaibi@gmail.com | 3 0583378725

Summary Objective:

A discipline, hard worker and fast learner. I have a bachelor's degree of Computer Science. Specialist member in the Saudi Council of Engineers. I can adapt to different situations and take the best out of each experience. Looking forward to obtaining a responsible and challenging position within the Company to give the best quality service and to work for a renowned organization that offers a challenging job where I can present my talent and skills and admires innovation.

Work Experience:

- Deanship of Communications and Information Technology at Imam Abdulrahman bin Faisal University (Namaa Co. for Computers, Communications and IT)
 - **Technical Support Specialist**

(Apr 2020 - Jan 2022)

- ➤ Maintenance hardware & software to university equipment, Installation and Support on printers. Installing cards and expansion cards.
- ➤ Install, configure and support LANs, WANs and Internet systems.
- ➤ Support network issue and IP-Phone problems and Solving problems by ERP System "Saned".
- Preparing and equipping computers and software for the employees and computer labs.
- ➤ Worked as *Team leader* for Development and Innovation Division which focus on updating policies, roles and procedures, creating plans.
- > Analyze platform data and solutions.
- ALKHALEEJ for Training and Educations

Technical Support & Network Admin

(Oct 2016 - Apr 2020)

- Maintenance the Institute's equipment and printers (Hardware & Software) Perform routine archive and backups.
- Analyze and solve problems. Troubleshooting and Backup scheduling.
- ➤ Provide simplified courses or workshops to enable branch staff to learn how to use computer applications.
- ➤ Manage and monitor the work of the corporate computer network and related Windows Servers.
- Managing the network and coordinating permissions and authorizations.

Computer & Network Instructor

(Sep 2013 –Apr 2020)

- Training high school graduates and qualifying them for a diploma in networking technology by training them in network management skills, sets up, configures, supports networks and troubleshoots network performance issues.
- > Training the clients on the skills of using computers in the office work.
- Administrative works. Knowledge about HR, Feasibility study & conducting interviews for new trainers and evaluating trainers.
- Establishing new training plans (Create and evaluate new Courses Outlines).

- Ahmad Nasser AlBinali & son's for Trading & Contracting Co. (Oct 2011- May 2012)
 Data Entry
 - Employee Affairs. Work on Employee files. Issuance and renewal of ARAMCO cards.

Academic Qualifications:

• Bachelor's degree of Computer Science from Qassim University 2009AD.

Courses & Professional Certifications:

- **Specialist** membership in the **Saudi Council of Engineers** With membership ID **779514**, valid to date **11/08/2024**.
- Certificate of completion Training in ITIL v4 Foundation.
- Training course PMP: about 35 hours (8-12 Sep 2019).
- **Human Resources Management** course from Central of Human Resources Professionals for Training about 20 hours (8 Aug 2019).
- Own **TOT** certified.
- Cisco Academy Instructor Certified.
- CCNA R&S: Scaling Networks (ScaN), Connecting Networks (CN), Routing and Switching Essentials (RSE) & Introduction to Networks (ITN) from Cisco Academy (Apr 2019 & Dec 2018). Prepared to be passing CCNA: Routing and Switching.
- Cisco Networking Academy® Cybersecurity Essentials from Cisco 2018.
- Information Technology Essentials (ITE) from Cisco Academy (5 of May 2016).
- CompTIA A+(30 of June 2015).
- Cambridge diploma in information technology 28, Apr 2014.
- MAHARA Program (The Community Service & Continuing Education Center in Prince Mohammad Bin Fahd University and with Wipro Arabia Ltd.) (6 months)

Skills:

Computer Skills:

- I have a good knowledge in writing Feasibility study for new projects.
- ➤ IT savvy, Familiar dealing with Trouble shooting of Operating Systems (Windows, MAC, LINUX OS), Network Support and Computer Maintenance. Active Directly Group Policy implementation.
- ➤ Full knowledge in Office Application, SharePoint, Programming, Databases (Oracle Systems) and Designing.
- > Support site staff with remote IT assistance.

Personal Skills:

- ➤ Great Interpersonal and communication skills and dealing with a team.
- Leadership skills. Creativity & Able to work under pressure.
- ➤ Highly organized, planning and time management.
- ➤ Dependable, adaptability, Commitment to continuous learning and development and have a position, attention to details.